麦克斯 你的男朋友正裸身
Max, your boyfriend is naked
从他称为公寓的垃圾箱家中跟你招手
and waving from the dumpster he calls his apartment.
先看清是不是他
Make sure it's Deke.
上次你也这么说 结果我过去
Last time you said that, I went over,
那人只是个在普通垃圾箱里裸体的瘾君子
and it was just a naked meth head in a normal dumpster.
虽然也爽了一晚 但还是要看清楚
I mean, we had a blast, but still.
好歹那瘾君子还买过不少小蛋糕
Well, at least that meth head bought a bunch of cupcakes.
虽然他是以为小蛋糕是活物
I mean, he thought they were alive,
但好歹有掏钱买啊
but he bought them.
我要提早闪人了
Hey, I'm gonna cut out early.
你又要去过夜吗
You're sleeping over again?
不是吧 麦克斯 真又去睡垃圾箱吗
Seriously, Max, sleeping in a dumpster?
你是想让非典卷土重来吗
Are you trying to bring SARS back?
非典也是我第一时间传进美国的
Well, I did bring it in the first time,
那也是我最后一次
And that is the last time I hook up
在泰国跟蝙蝠瞎搞
with a bat in Thailand.
麦克斯
Hey, Max.
麦克斯迟到45分钟了
Max is 45 minutes late.
她最好别再说是去做前列腺检查了
And she better not say she have a prostate exam
这次我不会再上当受骗了[男人才有]
'cause I'm not falling for that again.
别这样 她就在隔壁迪克家
Relax, she's just down the street at Deke's place.
你应该懂当你新处一个对象的时候
You know how it is when you first start sleeping with somebody,
都会爱不释手 整天想腻在一起
and you can't keep your hands off each other.
总之你信我说的就行了
Yeah, just take my word for it.
我就对我的初恋"爱不释手"
I know I couldn't keep my hands off my first love.
当然 我说的是我的"大雕"
I'm talking, of course, about my penis.
我受够了
I've had enough!
有你们俩妞这么踩我的吗
You two girls walk all over me.
连个婴儿都能踩你吧
A baby can walk all over you.
大家安安
Hi, everybody.
我刚听到了俩流浪汉在垃圾箱里瞎搞呢
I just heard two hobos getting freaky in the garbage.
苏菲 那是麦克斯跟迪克
Sophie, that was Max and Deke.
我懂了
Oh, I get it.
要玩点刺激 才能保持新鲜感
You gotta do crazy things to keep it fresh.
我曾经试过在巴士上跟人乱搞
You know, I once had sex on a bus,
而且我还是司机哦
and I was driving it.
可惜啊 车上的孩子上学还是迟到了
Boy, were those kids late to school.
够了 我要杀过去那里
That's it, I am marching over there
跟麦克斯谈判
and putting my foot down with Max.
没人能在我的上班钟点乱搞
No one has sex on my clock.
可能是因为你的"钟点"不够大
Well, maybe your clock's not big enough.
够了 以后你没免费果冻吃了
That's it. No more free jell-o.
麦克斯
Max!
麦克斯 开门
Max, open up.
我现在超火大
I'm very upset.
比你上次替我报名
More upset than that time
参加少年棒球联盟还火大
you enrolled me in little league.
但是你自己决定要打完整季的啊
Hey, it was your decision to play the full season.
太好了 我最低潮的时候正"想要"有人
Oh, goody, I was hoping for some hecklers at this,
在旁唧唧歪歪呢
my lowest moment.
如果垃圾箱在晃动
Hey, if the dumpster's rockin',
敲破门也没人理你
don't bother knockin', baby.
你好 小兄弟
Hey, man.
你好 女童军
Hello, little girl.
我要三盒萨摩亚与一盒薄荷口味饼干
I'll take three boxes of samoas and a thin mints.
我也要盒香花巧
Don't forget my tagalongs.
现在那口味是叫"香草花生巧克力"
They're called peanut butter patties now.
我为啥要这么讨打
Why must I be that person?
你们好啊 呆瓜们
What up, fools?
你好啊 小荡妇
Hey, girl.
麦克斯 你上班迟到48分钟了
Max, you're 48 minutes late for work.
张君雅小妹妹
Look, little Debbie,
我们是在这忙着准备
We're in here preparing for
明天烘焙学校的重要比赛
a big pastry school competition tomorrow.
以及做爱
And having sex.
如果你胆敢怒犯姐威 打扰姐学习
And if you ever interrupt me while I am studying...
以及做爱
And having sex.
姐就要把你那擦了爽身粉的屁屁
Again, I will dropkick your baby-powdered ass
给踢回去 跟其他哈比人团聚
back to the shire with the other hobbits.
我警告她了
I told her.
有咩
Did you?
蛋糕花得在我们喊"时间到"前
All flowers must be set on top of the cakes
就统统摆上蛋糕
by the time we call "time."
大伙们 最后装饰[摸]
Everyone, final touches.
这句话也是我还在
That's what I used to say
猫头鹰餐厅打工时下班前会说的
when I finished my shift at Hooters.
性感啊 那制服还有留着吗
Hot. You still got that uniform?
不知道还合身不
Oh, not sure it'd fit me anymore.
我以前可是有对超巨乳
I used to have really big boobs.
碧碧 还剩多少时间
Bebe, how much time is there left?
我们所有人吗
For all of us?
天啊 我们最多还剩两个月可以活吧
Oh, oh, gosh, I'd say two months, tops.
不是 我是说蛋糕比赛
No, no, for the cake competition.
还剩60秒
Oh, 60 seconds.
只剩60秒了 不是吧
Only 60 seconds? Come on!
抱歉 我承受不了这么大压力
I'm sorry, I can't handle this pressure.
再这么紧张下去
It's only a matter of time
我很快又要开始吃自己的眼睫毛了
before I start eating my eyelashes again.
赢了的队伍可以免一周的学费
The winning team will earn a free week of class.
而且还有 怎么说呢 可以使劲显摆
and also--how do you say-- bragging rights.
快点啊
Hurry!
动作快点 琳赛·罗韩[手慢]
Move faster, Lindsay Slow-hands.
放弃吧 大玛丽
Forget about it, big Mary.
这比赛我们赢定了
These competition is ours.
迪克跟我都是穷逼 我们比你更需要赢
Deke and I are broke. We need this more than you.
倒数15秒
15 seconds!
你好啊 卡洛琳
Bonjour, Caroline.
见到你真是赏心悦目
This is a real treat.
少来这套 你结婚了
Don't do that. You're married.
我来这里纯粹是为了公事
I'm only here in an official capacity.
碧碧理智线断了 在走廊里发疯呢
Bebe's in an emotional ball in the hall.
倒数10秒
Ten seconds!
加油 妹子
Come on, girl.
把花放上去 快放上去
Bring it home, bring it home!
我对这事真是亢奋过头了
I am way too excited about this.
好了各位
Okay, everybody.
最好的蛋糕花很明显了
I see a clear favorite here.
但卡洛琳 说实话
But, Caroline, in truth,
如果是要我选这里最漂亮的一朵花
if I were to pick the prettiest flower in the room,
我会选你
I'd pick you.
那...不是明摆着的吗
That is...incredibly obvious
你的选择十分正确
and incredibly accurate.
克制点 好歹去楼梯间再搞吧
Oh, come on! Get a stairwell!
-你的计时表 -谢谢
- Your timer. - Merci.
快说谁赢了吧
Just tell us who won.
我很高兴宣布 赢家是
The winners are, I am very happy to say...
麦克斯与迪克
Max and Deke.
你刚才太牛了 我爱你
You were amazing! I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
等等 真的吗
Wait, you do?
那你说真的吗
Do you?
没错 我是啊
Yeah...I do.
好吧 我也是
Yeah, well, I do too,
恭喜你倒大霉啦
So suck on that.
好吧 两件重要的事
Okay, two important things.
一 我就是在百合网上跟你聊的那个人
One, I'm the guy you've been talking to on OkCupid.
二 我想跟你有五分钟的姐妹淘聊天时间
And two, I need five minutes of girl talk
五分钟就好
and not a minute more
因为时间多了 我怕我会变成女人
because I'm worried it'll turn me into a girl.
来 说吧
Go. Tell me.
知无不言 言无不尽
Leave nothing out, leave everything in.
我今天说了一句我从没想过会说的话
I said something today I never thought I'd say.
"谢谢"吗
"Thank you"?
我对迪克说"我爱你"了
I said "I love you" to Deke.
是他先说"我爱你" 然后我也说了
He said, "I love you," and I said it back.
很好 恭喜你
Oh, cool. Good for you.
等等 就这样吗
Wait, that's it?
我最终决定低下头跟你当闺蜜
I finally decide to cave and be a girl for you,
你就这么把我晾着吗
and you hang me out to dry?
我看过电影好吗
I've seen movies.
你应该是要跳起来然后说
You're supposed to jump around and say,
"鸡尾酒庆祝时间到啦"
"this calls for a Margarita!"
This calls for a Margarita!
太假也太晚
Too much, too late.
你的第一反应就说明了一切
Your first reaction said everything,
而你的第二反应只是让人恶心
and your second one was just annoying.
对不起嘛 我只是没想到
I'm sorry, I just didn't think
你会对他这么认真
you were taking him so seriously.
他一毛钱都没有
He has no money.
这家伙就住在垃圾箱里呢
I mean, the man lives in a dumpster.
你真势利眼
You are such a snob.
你不觉得他每到收垃圾的日子
It doesn't bother you he has to move his house
就得把他的垃圾箱挪走很烦吗
every Tuesday between 10:00 and 2:00?
没 我一生放荡不羁爱旅游
No, I've always wanted to travel.
你不是吧 你不会真的是爱他吧
Come on, you can't really be in love with him, right?
你怎么能爱上迪克
I mean, you can't love Deke.
麦克斯 你爱上那咖啡色皮肤 犹太爆炸头
Max, you're in love with that cute mochaccino homeless guy
无家可归的小伙了吗
with the jew-fro?
他才不是无家可归
He is not homeless.
他住在一个装修精美的垃圾箱里
He lives in a beautifully decorated dumpster.
也就是无家可归
So homeless?
我理解你
I get it.
我以前也曾经跟
You know, I used to be engaged
一个住在下水道的男人订过婚
to a man who lived in the sewers.
没办法 心之所向 身之所往
Yeah, the heart wants what it wants.
而且他说他跟
Plus he told me he was friends
"忍者龟"们是好友[住下水道]
with The Mutant Ninja Turtles,
当年他们可是风靡全球啊
and they were a huge deal at the time.
什么当年
At the time?
如果他能介绍我跟紫乌龟认识 麻烦跟他复合
If he can introduce me to Donatello, get him back.
那你怎么知道你是不是真的爱这个...下水道男
How did you know you loved this...sewer man?
他总能让我笑
Well, he made me laugh.
他也热情四射
He was very passionate,
还我无时无刻都想跟他黏在一起
and I wanted to be with him constantly.
可能因为他让我染上海洛因毒瘾吧
Probably because he got me hooked on heroin.
那一年的夏天真疯狂
That was a crazy summer.
你看 我也有这种感觉
See? I feel the same way.
可惜的是 没有海洛因这一部分
Minus the heroin part, unfortunately.
我能用一下你的厕所吗
Can I use your bathroom?
我想嘘嘘 可是我家厕所里有胡蜂
I have to tinkle, and there's a wasp in mine.
去吧 苏菲
Go ahead, Sophie.
你那是什么眼神
What's that look?
胡蜂在我背后吗
Is the wasp behind me?
我真不敢相信
I can't believe you.
你都跟我做了3年的朋友了
Even after three years of being friends with me,
你心里还是歧视穷人
you still have a thing against poor people.
麦克斯 你爱他 我也能喜欢他
Max, you love him, I can love him.
但我需要多了解他一点
I just have to get to know him better.
邀请我去那垃圾箱里
Invite me over to the garbage can
办一个奶酪美酒派对啊
for a wine and cheese party.
等等 奶酪美酒派对吗
Wait a minute. Wine and cheese party?
我要带我的新男宠过去
Oh, I'm gonna bring my new boy toy.
他是自助餐店里的凯撒色拉撒胡椒专员
He's the caesar salad pepperer at the Olive Garden.
不能带伴 苏菲
No dates, Sophie.
那里面小到
The place is so small,
我有一次不小心就放包里带回家了
I once accidentally took it home in my purse.
这卡忙贝尔奶酪一股脚臭味
This camembert smells like feet,
所以肯定是好货
so you know it's good.
你看你 芝士堡市长
Look at you, Mayor McCheese.
真奢华
So fancy.
就是餐厅的熟人而已嘛
It's just the usual diner crew, you know.
我们餐厅里卖假的假蟹肉呢
We serve imitation imitation crab.
只是想为你提高一下这里的档次嘛
Well, I just wanted to class the place up for you.
摆上葡萄酒和奶酪 外加上完厕所冲水
You know, get some wine, get some cheese, flush.
你不用这么大费周章啦
You did not need to do that.
我爱你住在这里
I love that you live here.
我一生下来就不介意被扔在垃圾箱里
And if a dumpster was good enough for me as a baby,
所以现在的我也不会介意住这里
it is still good enough for me as an adult.
你"爱"我住在这里啊
Oh, you love that I live here.
你还有"爱"别的东西吗
Do you love anything else?
我以前也爱《功夫小子》这部电影啊
Well, I loved the Karate Kid movies
直到后来被威尔史密斯的儿子毁了
until will smith's kid ruined them.
我们能正经说两句吗
Okay, can we please be serious for a minute?
你说"我也爱你"时 是因为我先说的吗
Did you just say "I love you" because I said it first?
老实说 的确是
Look, honestly, yes.
但不只是顺口回答 是真心的吧
But I definitely meant it, I think.
表白我很不在行
Look, I suck at this stuff.
看到小孩跌倒不笑的功力也很差
This and not laughing when kids fall.
但如果有天 或当我再说出口时
Just know that if/when I say it again,
我绝对是真心的
I will mean it.
我能等 我爱你 麦克斯
I can totally wait-- I love you, Max.
你这招还真"隐晦"啊
Nice try, sneaky.
你来啦 进来吧
Oh, hi. Come on in.
别毒舌 你那张床也不是真正的床
And be nice. Remember, you barely have a bed.
别紧张 我好喜欢这一区
Don't worry. I love this area.
我见到你邻居了 那张床垫
I met your neighbor, the mattress.
那"女王"[尺寸]吗
Oh, that queen?
要解百纳还是西拉
So would you like a cabernet or a shiraz?
稀拉
Shiraz.
真有葡萄酒叫这个啊
Oh, that's a real name?
这里的搭配挺有意思的
Some interesting pairings here.
其实我眼前这对情侣也是
In fact, I'm looking at one as we speak.
神啊 赶紧让下一位客人来敲门吧
Please, someone else come right now.
大家好啊
Hi, everyone!
我来啦
I'm here.
赶紧让下一位客人来敲门吧
Please, someone else come right now.
我带了点自制的泡菜煎饼
I brought some homemade kimchi bin dae duk.
你们想试试吗
Would you like to try it,
还是要我直接扔进垃圾箱里
or should I just throw it right into the garbage?
以前这里面也有这臭味 我花了一年才散掉
It took me a year to get this kind of smell out of here,
但还是谢谢了 阿憨
but thanks, Han.
真像个垃圾堆
Oh, what a dump.
这双关是我在来的路上想的
I thought of that on the way over.
大伙开始吧
All right, let's do this.
我准备好要彻夜狂欢啦
I'm ready to rage all night, baby.
靠 不是吧
Oh, hell no.
这不适合我这把老骨头
I am too old for this.
苏菲 小心头
Sophie, watch your head.
你可能得脱下你的高跟鞋
You might wanna take your heels off.
脱下我的高跟鞋
Take my heels off?
当年苏联入侵都不能要姐脱下高跟鞋
Communist Russia couldn't get me to take my heels off.
厄尔 你想去一个我们想"弯腰"才"弯腰"
Hey, Earl, you wanna go get drunk somewhere
不用听人指挥的地方买醉吗
we don't have to bend over till we want to?
正有此意
Indeed, I do.
我不是要炫耀 但是我是这里面
Not to brag, but I'm the only one
唯一能把腰板挺直的人
who can stand up in here.
的确值得炫耀 阿憨
Cool brag, Han.
迪克 跟我说说你吧
So, Deke, tell me about yourself.
不许采用最高监狱的讯问手段 审问他
Hey, stop Guantanamo bay-ing him.
我在烘焙学校学习
Well, I go to pastry school,
我住在垃圾箱里
I live in a dumpster,
我因为长得太帅 被英国男子组合
and I was thrown out of One Direction
"一世代"踢出乐队
for being too handsome.
就这么多
That's about it.
肯定不止这么多
There must be more to you than that.
因为在一个垃圾箱派对上
I mean, I'm surprised to see
居然会出现洛克福奶酪搭配
a roquefort cheese paired with a 2001 Syrah
法国罗纳河谷的2001年的西拉葡萄酒
from the Rhone region of France at a dumpster party.
你对葡萄酒的了解是在哪里学的
Where'd you learn about wine?
我想给你留下好印象
Well, I wanted to impress you,
恰好对成年人的葡萄汁有些了解罢了
and I keep my adult grape juice game on point.
你到底来自哪里
So where are you from originally?
你是在仓库里长大 还是...
Did you grow up in a storage facility or--
别问了行吗
Will you stop?
他紧张的样子就像生日派对上的胖子
He looks nervous like the fat guy at a birthday party
突然发现大家得下小泳池玩
when he finds out there's a pool.
来了 来了
Coming, coming.
还好 我们找对垃圾箱了
Good. We have the right dumpster.
我带了瓶葡萄酒 碧碧带了奶酪
I brought some wine. Bebe brought cheese.
勉强算是奶酪吧
Kind of.
各位 非常感谢你们能邀请我
Hey, guys, thanks for inviting me.
很开心加入你们
Happy to be included.
好的 又来一个妞
All right, another babe.
把你的钥匙扔进碗里[选玩伴]
Throw your keys in the bowl.
现在里面只有我和阿憨的钥匙
Right now, it's just me and Han, and...
你别做梦了
that ain't happening.
尼可拉斯来这里干嘛 快把我藏起来
What is Nicolas doing here? Hide me.
无论怎样 他都会看见你的
I think you're gonna run into him.
抱歉 我以为你喜欢他呢
Sorry, I thought you were into him.
我才不喜欢他
I'm not into him.
拜托 卡洛琳 别紧张
Please, Caroline, relax.
这只是个派对 我们只是朋友
It's just a party. I'm here as a friend.
那你的手放在哪儿呢
Then where is your hand?
放在你美丽的翘臀上
On your beautiful bottom.
抱歉 这太挤了
Sorry, it's crowded.
我的手要么放着上面 要么就放水槽里
It was either there or in the sink.
请你拿开你的手
Please remove it.
拿开了啊
I-I did.
那是我的手 宝贝
That one's mine, baby.
拜托 现在都晚上8点45分了
Come on, it's 8:45,
大家居然还衣冠整齐地站在那里
and nobody's got their tops off.
得有人采取点行动才行
Somebody's gotta do something.
我曾玩过"天堂7分钟"这个游戏
Oh, one time I played Seven Minutes in Heaven.
就是我被一辆巴士撞了
Well, I got hit by a bus,
然后昏死过去7分钟
and I was dead for seven minutes.
碧碧 你想来点葡萄酒吗
Bebe, do you want some wine?
好啊
Sure, why not?
反正我明天也没事做
I don't have anything to do tomorrow
除了要搬去加拿大
except move to Canada.
什么
What?
不是什么大事啦
Yeah, no biggie.
长话短说
Long story short,
他们发现了我
They found me.
卡洛琳 看来以后办公室
Caroline, looks like it's gonna be just
就剩咱们俩了
you and me in the office.
尼可拉斯 别这样
Nicolas, please.
我刚都说手不要乱放
What did I tell you about your hand?
那是我的手
That's me!
我只是想挤过那边去吃奶酪而已
I was trying to push my way to the cheese.
碧碧 如果你去了亚伯达省[加拿大]
Hey, Bebe gun, if you're ever in Alberta,
记得去班夫的费尔蒙酒店 超级好玩
hit the Fairmont at Banff-- super fun.
我曾喝醉了 然后冲进那边的湖里
I got wasted and cannonballed into the lake there once.
当时湖面结冰了 我盆骨都碎了
It was frozen. Shattered my pelvis.
美好的时光啊
Good times.
我知道那地方
Hey, I know that place.
路易斯湖城堡酒店吧
Fairmont Chateau on Lake Louise?
我们以前冬天常去那边玩
We used to winter there.
那可是一个非常豪华的度假酒店
That's a really exclusive resort.
我有一次看见他们让芭芭拉·史翠珊[著名女星]
I once saw them tell Barbra Streisand
去住普通的假日酒店
to take it to the Holiday Inn.
卡洛琳 你想尝尝我的三重奶酪[精液]吗
Caroline, you want some of my triple creme?
我不想尝你的任何"东西"
I don't want any of your creme.
这里开始越来越挤了
You know what, it's getting a little crowded in here.
我要趁人不注意时 偷偷溜走
I'm just gonna slip out without anyone noticing.
让一下
Oh, excuse me.
借过 借过 借过
Excuse me, excuse me, excuse me.
等下 等下 先别走
Wait, wait, wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
那你觉得
So...
迪克怎么样 你现在喜欢他了吗
Deke--what do you think? Do you like him now?
在今晚之前
Well, before tonight,
我以为他是一个在大街上闲晃
I thought he was the guy who walks around
还一边高歌"当你回到家
singing "When you're sliding into home
屎全拉裤子里"的腹泻之歌的小屁孩
and your shorts are full of foam, diarrhea."
现在我发现他很了解奶酪
Now I find out he knows all about cheese
而且他还去过要价不菲的度假酒店
and has been to this massively expensive resort,
这让我更加困惑了
so I'm even more confused.
有什么好困惑的
What's confusing?
因为腹泻 屎才会拉裤子里啊
The foam is diarrhea.
卡洛琳 等等
Caroline, wait.
-我送你回去吧 -不必 我自己可以回去
- Let me walk with you. - No, no, no. I'm good.
那至少戴上我的围巾 现在很冷
Please, at least take my scarf. It's cold.
不用了 我不冷
No, I'm fine--
-你没事吧 我来扶你 -不用了 尼可拉斯
- Are you okay? Here, let me help. - No, Nicolas.
我不会当小三的
I am not going to be the other woman.
虽然我现在正躺在垃圾堆里
Despite the fact that I am literally lying in trash,
但我不是那种垃圾女人
I am not trashy.
卡洛琳 听着
Caroline, listen.
事情并不总是像表面看起来那样
Things aren't always what they seem.
因为它从表面看是个垃圾箱
Just because that is garbage on the outside
并不意味着它里面
doesn't mean that it cannot be
不能是一间装修精美的公寓
a nice apartment on the inside.
因为我从表面上看似已婚
Just because I'm married on the outside
并不意味着我心里面真的有我老婆
doesn't mean I'm married on the inside.
人生很复杂
Life is complex.
你的整个理论都是基于我会认为
Your whole thesis is hinged on the fact
那个垃圾箱里面装修得还不错
that I think that dumpster is nice on the inside,
但我我一点也不这么认为 晚安
which I don't. Good night.
-卡洛琳 -尼可拉斯 别求了
- Oh, Caroline-- - Nicolas, please don't beg.
-我是想说 -或许下辈子吧
- I just-- - Maybe another world, another life.
-我想 -你不能为了我而抛弃你的老婆
- I want-- - You can't leave your wife for me.
-不是的 -说真的 你什么都不必说了
- No, it's just-- - Seriously! You don't have to say it.
不 我一定要说
No, I do.
你衣服后面粘上纸尿布了
You have a diaper on your back.
我知道
I am aware.
你在那弄什么呢
What are you working on there?
是一家人在公园里野餐吗
Is that a family having a picnic at a park?
不 这是字母"G"
No, it's the letter "G"!
从1996年开始 我就没怎么用手写过字
I haven't written anything by hand since 1996.
我的字可是很牛哦
Well, my writing's really good.
我伪造过很多支票和医药处方
I forge a lot of checks and prescriptions.
我也算是个著名"医生"
I'm kind of a famous doctor.
你真的说出来了
You're really saying it.
你写的是 "我爱你"
That says, "I love you."
不 这是卡戴珊她妹在玩风帆
No, it's Khloe Kardashian windsurfing.
没错 迪克 我爱你
Yes, Deke, I love you.
碧碧
Oh, Bebe.
我还以为你今天要走 不会来办公室了
I wasn't expecting you today. I thought you moved.
我是要走啊 我的车就在外面
I'm on my way. My car's outside,
但我想起来我把药落在这里了
but I remembered I left my medication here.
好了 大袋的在哪里呢
Okay, now where's the big one?
既然你在这
Well, as long as you're here,
你能告诉我学生的财务档案放在哪里吗
could you show me where the student financial files are?
当然 它们被放在一个
Sure, they're here in this folder
名为"压抑"的文件夹
I've labeled "depressing."
我想看看迪克是不是靠奖学金念书
I wanna check Deke's file and see if he's on scholarship.
他怎么可能靠奖学金念书
He's definitely not on scholarship.
他家超级有钱 他是布朗伯格家族的
His family's super rich. He's a Bromberg.
等等 碧碧 你是说布朗伯格吗
Wait, Bebe. Bromberg?
迪克的姓不是"伯格"吗
I thought Deke's last name was just "Berg."
像是"冰山"或"皮茨" 就两个字
As in "Ice" Or "Pitts."
不是 他用"伯格"是为了省事
No, he just goes by Berg for short.
像我 我的全名是碧碧碧碧
You know, like me, my full name is Bebebebe.
所以你是说迪克是布朗伯格家族的
So you're telling me Deke is from the Bromberg family,
就是那个著名的布朗伯格电梯
As in the Bromberg elevators--
全市每一栋大楼用的电梯都是他们生产的
the ones that are in every building in the city?
就是那个在纽约医院有以布朗伯格
As in the Bromberg colo-rectal center
命名的肛肠检查中心吗
at the New York hospital?
没错
Yeah.
我曾在那丢过一个钱包
You know, I once left a purse
还切掉过我两英尺的大肠
and 2 feet of my large intestine there.
很高兴认识你 再见
Nice knowing you. Bye.
我马上回来
Ooh, I'll be right back.
如果你把我们的奶油搞砸
If you mess up our batter,
我会把你那玩意切下来
I'll cut your thing off.
好啊 少个5磅对我来说没什么关系
Sweet, I could stand to lose 5 pounds.
我有个好消息要跟你分享
I have some exciting news to share.
除非是关于淡季的三叶草奶昔
Unless it's about an off-season shamrock shake,
否则我不感兴趣
I don't care.
你的迪克 垃圾箱迪克
Your Deke--dumpster Deke--
真名叫迪肯·布朗伯格
is actually Deacon Bromberg.
是曼哈顿布朗伯格家族的 他是有钱人
of the Manhattan Brombergs! He's rich!
你在瞎说什么 这太扯了吧
What are you talking about? That is crazy.
如果他是有钱人 我会知道
I would know if he were rich.
我绝不会对一个有钱人说我爱他
I wouldn't have just told a rich guy I love him.
资料都在这里 是不是很棒
It's all right here. Isn't this amazing?
感觉就像你买了一条喜欢的裙子
This is like buying a dress you love
结果发现这裙子很有钱
and finding out it's rich.
你干嘛这样做
Whoa, why'd you do that?
-谁让你是有钱人 -麦克斯 别走
- You're rich. - Max, wait.
你还在那装穷 骗子
You pretended to be poor. Liar.
我的老天
Ooh, lordy be.
我就是爱看这样的戏码
This kind of drama's the reason
所以我才退出俄亥俄州立大学足球队
why I quit the Ohio state football team.
你为什么这么郁闷
Why are you so upset?
隐瞒自己是个有钱人是最善意的谎言了
Lying about being rich is at most a little white lie.
这是我听过最白痴的谎言
It is literally the whitest lie I have ever heard,
这事很严重
and it's a huge deal.
我从来不会爱上一个有钱人
I never would have fallen in love with someone who has money.
我们真是超级非常
We are drastically, massively,
十分不同的人
monumentally different people.
-麦克斯 能说句话吗 -我不知道
- Hey, Max, can we talk? - Oh, I don't know.
那要看跟谁说话了
Depends on who I'm talking to.
我是跟迪克 还是迪肯·布朗伯格
Am I talking to Deke or Deacon Bromberg,
电梯大王讲话
the elevator king?
天啊 如果你因为钱反应就这样
Man, if you're this upset about the money,
如果你发现我其实是女人的话
how are you gonna react when you find out
那反应会是怎么样
I'm really a woman?
我们不介意的
We wouldn't care.
在我们互诉爱意之前
I never tell anybody I'm rich
我从未告诉别人我的家世
until after we say I love you
因为我不想让钱改变任何东西
because I don't want money to change anything.
钱能改变一切
Money changes everything!
恕我失陪
Now excuse me.
我要忙我第二份工作的事了
I gotta do my second job,
想必你对这方面完全没有过体验吧
which you wouldn't know anything about.
你不是得去个啥领巾大会之类的吗
Don't you have an ascot convention to get to?
我还在
Still here.
你们来了两个客人呢
Also, two customers just showed up.
我们才不需要他们的钱
We don't need their money!
我们也是假装穷人的大骗子
We're big, fat liars pretending to be poor too.
没错 我妈发明了狗
Mm, yeah, my mom invented dogs.
只要有人买狗 就会有一成卖价进我们的口袋
Any time someone buys a dog, we get 10%!
现在换我不敢相信了
Now I can't believe it.
你都跟我做了3年的朋友了
Even after three years with me as a friend,
你心里还是仇视有钱人
you still have a thing against rich people.
没错 因为有钱人都是混蛋
I do, because rich people suck.
他们觉得自己强过所有人
They think they're better than everyone
而且通常都是烂人
and are generally sucky.
所以他有钱 姐不想要
So he has money, I don't want it.
又一次证明你我完全是两类人
Again, just wildly different people.
麦克斯 因为他表面看起来是有钱人
And, Max, just because he's rich on the outside
不代表他内心里面跟你就不一样啊
doesn't mean he's not like you on the inside.
人生很复杂
Life is complex.
我现在不想看到你
I don't wanna see you right now!
我也不想看到你
Hey! I don't wanna see you either.
给我丢些里面有奶油的
Just toss me something chocolate
巧克力口味小蛋糕就行
with some cream in the middle.
说到里面有奶油[精液]
And speaking of cream in the middle,
你的无家可归小男友想吸引你注意呢
your little homeless boyfriend is trying to get your attention.
他不是无家可归 他也不是我男朋友
He's not homeless. He's not my boyfriend.
他是有钱人
He's rich.
有钱人 而且还单身吗
Rich? And he's single?
看来姐还是去"脱下高跟鞋"吧
Oh, maybe I will take off my heels.